hi brother
you help me quickly
please hand
day thirty six
while the method is not ready
I'm going to invest in my truffle farmer
O Juninho
you can get 1 cup of coffee here
if i buy a little more
now i'm going to level three
that helped to do the sales
Trojan horse is
came to twenty-five percent
and today I'm going to the third level
chocolate hand
twenty-eight percent profit
march in progress let's go
and the method takes
it's not like that
is on
requires study
as much as I understand the creative process
I need to come up with something that works for the person
in my products
my subscription is worth more than the sale knows
monday
i have to deliver a marketing project
the guy even paid me
but now I go there old man haha
hey turned
Declaration of New
the doctor is there
oh that what before and after the hour
hey you're fine my dear
you catch the crowd like that with an open mind
it's easier for you to bring a strategic plan
now I'm going to study parade with the guy
ah no chevas
let's go to this New no Guy
my sky god
will pass
passed
we're here for like 2 hours bro
then I bought 1 lot of truffle
hospitalized car
it was already bro
I'm out of a car now with 1 lot of truffles
and now I will give
1 walk
until you get to the post
when I go through some perrenguezão like that
in life
mess with your booking again
I'm glad I have a truffle farmer
so now i'm thinking about it bro
comes a from that one will do what
keep crying
walking
will rain
wet the truffle
separate time to work and time to think
otherwise you won't leave the place
ah I'm passing on the perrengue well done
is an indication that I need to do something
not to pass the perrengue
until tomorrow
it was already bro
the car was bad
mkoa WA kagera